Guide to the Matthew F. McHugh papers, 1974-1992.
McHugh, Matthew F papers
- District Issues, 1978 - 1982 (Box 268)
  Cornell Miscellaneous 1979, Cornell Miscellaneous 1980, Cornell Grant Awards 1978-80, Cornell Grant Awards 1979, Cornell Grant Awards 1981, Cornell Grant Awards 1982, Cornell Hydropower, Cornell National Science Foundation, Ulster County Community College, Tompkins Cortland Community College, Sullivan county Community college, SUNY Delhi, SUNY New Paltz, Economic Development Administration, D of Education, Education - Student Financial Aid, Energy Conservation, NYS D of Commerce, NYS D of Labor, NYS D of Agriculture, NYS D of Environmental Conservation: Conservation & Environmental Program 1978, Water Quality Management, State Trade Adjustment Assistance 1984-1985, Action/Peace Corps/VISTA volunteerism, D of Agriculture 1981 re NY/NJ Milk, Synthetic Fuels and Gasohol 1980-1981, Anti-Recession Fiscal Assistance, Army Corps of Engineers 1979-1981, Comprehensive Employment & Training Act, D of Energy, Solar Energy, Child Abuse, Community Services Administration, D of Commerce (Patents), Flood Assitance Information, Disaster Assistance Information 1975-1980, HUD & Earth Sheltered Homes.
- District Issues, 1978 - 1986 (Box 267)
  Ulster County: County Legislature, Ulster County: Human Resources, Ulster County: Hudson Valley Health Systems, Ulster County: Hudson Valley Professional Standards Review Organization (2 files), Ulster County: Lake Minnewaska (2 files), Ulster County: Marcy South, Ulster County: Plant Closing, Ulster County: Route 209 (2 files), Ulster County: Ulster Performing Arts Center, Ulster County: 1978 Small Business Administration Designation, Ulster County: Stewart Airport, Ulster County: Steamtown, Ulster County: Youth Conservation Corps Program, Ulster County: Accord, Ulster County: Accord - Unification Church, Ulster County: Boiceville - Al Highley Case, Ulster County: Coal Terminal Project 1982 (3 files), Ulster County: Town of Denning, Ulster County: Ellenville (5 files), Ulster County: Erpf Center Catskill Regional Study, Ulster County: 1980 Flooding, Ulster County: Gardiner, Ulster County: Hardenburgh, Ulster County: Highland Veteran’s National Cemetary, Ulster County: Pine Vole Control, Ulster County: Hurley, Ulster County: Kerhonkson, Ulster County: Kingston.
- District Issues, 1979 - 1980, 1981 - 1984 (Box 111)
  Prattsville Pumped Storage, Upper Delaware River (11 files).
- District Issues, 1979 - 1984 (Box 275)
  Two small binders on federal assistance to 27th District 1977-1978, Tompkins: Ithaca: Festival 1981, Tompkins: Ithaca: Paleontological Research Institution 1979, Tompkins: Ithaca: Cornell University 1982, Tompkins: Ithaca: Cornell University 1981, Tompkins: Ithaca: Cornell: UAW Strike 1981, Tompkins: Ithaca: Cornell: 1980, Tompkins: Ithaca: Ecosystem, Tompkins: Ithaca: Hydropower, Tompkins: Ithaca: Strand Theatre 1979, Tompkins: Transit: Greyhound, Tompkins: Slaterville Springs, Tompkins Cortland Community College, Watkins Glen Grand Prix, Tompkins: Ithaca: Waste Treatment Plant 1984, Tompkins: Out of District, Ulster: Miscellaneous 1983, Ulster: Miscellaneous 1982, Ulster: Miscellaneous 1981, Ulster: Miscellaneous 1980, Ulster: Miscellaneous 1979, Ulster: Miscellaneous 1978, Ulster: Catskill Gateway, Ulster: Wind Energy, Ulster: Hudson River PCB Reclamation, Ulster: Economic Development, Ulster: Exxon, Ulster: Federated Sportsmen’s Club, Ulster: Ulster County Community College Water Quality, Disaster Relief.
- District Issues, 1981 - 1985 (Box 105)
  Ulster - Kingston - Aarons 1983, Ulster - Kingston - Firemen’s Museum 1984, Ulster - Kingston - New Proposed Radio Station 1981, Ulster - Woodstock - John Godsey, Ulster - Woodstock - McGivern c1985, Ulster - Woodstock - Vietnam Vets Leichenmueller, Multi-County - Vietnam Vets Counseling 1982 - 1984, Multi-County - Walkill Basin NY/NJ, Multi-County - Flood Project, Walkill RR/Conrail Stephen Larsen 1986, Ulster - Shokan - Sherret Case 1981-1982, Ulster - Route 209 1981, Ulster - Rosendale - EDA and FmHA “Jobs Bill” Funds 1983, Ulster - Rosendale - Flood control Project 1984-1985, Ulster - Rosendale - Rosendale Mall Fire 1981, Ulster - Rondout Valley CS Asbestos 1983, Ulster - (Town of) Rochester - Unification Church, Multi-County - Prattsville Pumped Storage 1981 (see also Box 112), Multi-County - Prattsville Pumped Storage 1982 (see also Box 112), Multi-County - Prattsville Pumped Storage 1983 (see also Box 112), Multi-County - Prattsville Pumped Storage 1984 (see also Box 112), Sullivan - Neversink - Floods 1981, Sullivan - Mountain Pride Farms 1981, Sullivan - Liberty - Kingston Industries 1983, Sullivan - Healthcare - HSA Designation HMSA 1981, Sullivan - SCCC Title XII, Sullivan - Barry Batinkoff and Department of Labor, SBA 1981, SBA 1982, SBA 1983, SBA 1984, NYS Small Cities Development 1983, NYS Energy Office 1982, National Endowment for the Arts - Donald Knack 1984.
- District Issues, 1983 - 1990 (Box 298)
  F14 Airplane, Railroads: Pittsburgh & Lake Erie / Erie Lackawanna Purchase, Broome County: Port of Entry, Armed Services Committee Chairmanship1987, Multi-County: Rail Abandonments, Multi-County: D of Transportation and Conrail (2 files), 1983-1984 Projects Book, Army Corps of Engineers - Baltimore, Sample Letters, Mailings to Districts, District Project Mailings, Weekend Backups - Tompkins County, Weekend Backups - Delaware County, Weekend Backups - Broome County, Weekend Backups - Tioga County, Weekend Backups - Sullivan County, Delaware River 1986 (7 files), Broome County: Singer, Apache Helicopter D of Defense Appropriation, 5/90 Appropriation Slot, “McHugh”.
- District Issues, 1983 - 1992 (Box 167)
  Ellenville - Beerkill Flood April 1987, Cornell Theory Center Super Computer 1989, Newburgh-Beacon Bridge 1986 (6 files), Tompkins County Airport 1989 - 1992, Agriculture Appropriations FY 1988 (2 files), FmHA Housing Loans FY 1988 District Trip, FmHA Housing Programs 1986, Labourdette’s Report to Delegation 1985, FmHA NYS Rural Housing Problems, FmHA NYS Housing Funds FY 1987, FmHA FY 1988 Appropriations, FmHA FY 1988 NYS Office Administration Cuts, Agriculture Appropriations Oversight and Investigations 1983, WARNER, Susan (McHugh staffer) 1.5" thick file, FmHA Appropriati0ons Hearings FY 1986.
- District Issues 094, 1975 - 1977 (Box 55)
  Delaware River Basin Commission, Conrail Abandonment, Delaware River Releases Correspondence, Delaware River Releases 1977, Delaware River Releases Articles, Delaware River Releases Articles 1975-1976, Ellenville CETA Problem, Environmental Protection agency, Farmers Home Administration, Catskill Study Commission (2 files), Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, Community Development Corporation, Correspondence re Dept of Health, Education and Welfare, Correspondence re Dept of Housing & Urban Development, Correspondence re Dept of Interior, Correspondence re Dept of Justice, Correspondence re Dept of Labor, Correspondence re Dept of Transportation, Correspondence re Federal Energy Administration, Flood Insurance Program - General, Flood Insurance Program - Sullivan county, Flood Insurance Program - Ulster County, General Services Administration, Delaware County - Margaretville, Delaware County - Middletown - town, Delaware County - Miscellaneous, Delaware County - SUNY Access Road, Delaware County - Stamford, Delaware County - Miscellaneous Towns, Delaware County - West Branch and Delaware Pollution Project, Agricultural Stabilization & Conservation Service, ALTA Administration, American Revolution Bicentennial Administration, Amtrak, Appalachian Regional Commission, Community Action Commission to Help theEconomy, Civil Service Commission, D’ORTA, Frank, Delaware County - Catskill Hollow Road/Route 206, Delaware County - Margaretville Memorial Hospital, Delaware County - Delhi, Delaware County - Delaware Opportunities, Delaware County - Fleischmanns, Delaware County - Hamden, Delaware County - Hancock, Energy Research & Development Administration.
- District Issues 094, 1976 - 1977 (Box 85)
  All within Broome County, Endwell, Glen Aubrey, Johnson City - village, Kirkwood, Lisle, Maine, Woodburne Court, Interstate 88, D of Transportation, Rock Bottom Dam, Chenango School district, Metro Interfaith Services Inc., Action for Older Persons, Bicentennial Commission, Bicycle Demonstration Project, Fall 1977 Agricultural Disaster, Disaster Designation and Aid, Drug Awareness Center, Legal Services Corporation, Nanticoke Creek flooding, BARKER T., Binghamton 1975-1977, Binghamton School District, Binghamton Sewer Project, Binghamton 1977, Binghamton Community Development, Robeson Center for the Arts, Binghamton GAF Corporation, Chenango, Colesville, Conklin, Deposit - village, Dickinson - town, Endicott.
- District Issues 095, 1975 - 1977 (Box 58)
  Sullivan: Federal Prison, Sullivan: Fall 1977 Agricultural Disaster, Sullivan: New Horizons, Sullivan: Farmer’s Home Administration Mass Transportation, Sullivan: Stone Arch Bridge, Sullivan: County Planning Board, Sullivan: Walnut Mountain Nursing Home, Sullivan: Bethel, Sullivan: Bloomingburg, Sullivan: Callicoon, Sullivan: Cochecton, Sullivan: Delaware, Sullivan: Fallsburg, Sullivan: Highland, Sullivan: Liberty - town, Sullivan: Liberty - town sewer, Sullivan: Liberty - village, Sullivan: Liberty - village sidewalks, Sullivan: Liberty - village flooding, Sullivan: Neversink, Sullivan: Lumberland/Glen Spey, Sullivan: Mamakatink, Sullivan: Monticello, Sullivan: Monticello Housing Authority, Sullivan: Rockland, Sullivan: Roscoe, Sullivan: Thompson, Sullivan: Tusten, Sullivan: Woodridge Urban Renewal, Sullivan: Woodridge, Sullivan: Wurtsboro, Sullivan: Woodridge Sewer Plant, Tioga: Miscellaneous 1977, Tioga: Miscellaneous 1975-1976, Tioga: County Planning Board, Tioga: Flooding, Tioga: Barton - town, Tioga: Candor, Tioga: Nichols, Tioga: Owego, Tioga: Owego Town & Village Sewer, Tioga: Spencer - town, Tioga: Spencer - village, Tioga: Tioga - town, Tioga: Waverly Dry Brook Creek, Tioga: Waverly - village sewer, Tioga: Waverly - village water, Tompkins: Miscellaneous 1976-1977, Tompkins: 1977 Fall Agrciultural Disaster, Tompkins: Airport, Tompkins: Health Matters, Tompkins: Historical Society, Tompkins: Red X, Tompkins: Brooktondale, Tompkins: Caroline, Tompkins: Danby.
- District Issues 095, 1976 - 1977 (Box 127)
  Broome - Port Dickinson, Broome - Union (Town), Broome - Vestal, Broome - Vestal - Water Supply, Broome - Whitney Point, Broome - Windsor, Chemung - General/Miscellaneous, Chemung - National Fire Academy, Cnemung - Regional Housing Council, Chemung - Fall 1977 Agricultural Disaster, Chemung - Out-of-District Projects, Chemung - Erin, Chemung - Van Etten, Delaware - Cat Hollow Road, Delaware - SBA Disaster Decree 1977, Delaware - Bovina, Delaware - Colchester, Delaware - Delhi, Delaware - Delhi SUNY Access Road, Delaware - Deposit, Delaware - Fleishmanns, Delaware - Hamden, Delaware - Read Memorial Hospital, Delaware - Hancock, Delaware - Hobart, Delaware - Margaretville, Delaware - Middletown, Delaware - New Kingston, Delaware - Roxbury, Delaware - Stamford, Delaware - Walton, Delaware - Fall 1977 Agricultural Disaster, Sullivan - Miscellaneous Inquiries, Sullivan - Association for Retarded Children, Sullivan - Catskill Art Society, Sullivan - Cerebral Palsy Association 202 HUD Funds, Sullivan - Community General Hospital, Sullivan - HUD Community Develoipment 75-76, Sullivan - Family Court, Sullivan - Historical Society, Sullivan - International Airport, Sullivan - Airport Case, Sullivan - County Park, Sullivan - County Park: Dept of Interior Bureau Outdoor Recreation.
- District Issues 095, 1976 - 1977 (Box 255)
  HUD Section 8 Housing, HUD Home Ownership, HUD CDBG, HUD Rehabilitation Programs, HUD Small Cities Program, HUD College Housing, HUD Coop Housing, D of Interior, D of Justice, D of Labor, Law Enforcement Assistance Administration, Library Services Construction Act, LVT Delegation Letter, National Consumer Coop Bank, National Education Association, National Park Design, National Solar Heating/Cooling, Nuclear Regulatory Commission, Office of Management and Budget, PCBs, Davis-Bacon HUD Survey, Bruce Drazen Binghamton Business Assistance, Advin Corporation, Broome County: Miscellaneous (5 files), Broome County: Out of District, Broome County: Action for Older Persons, Broome County: Airport, Broome County: Brixius Creek, Broome County: Gypsy Moths 1982, Broome County: Ebonex (2 files), Broome County: Binghamton Housing Authority, Broome County: Binghamton Parlor City, Broome County: GAF Layoff Petition for TRA, Broome County: GAF Power Plant, Broome County: GAF Retirees, Broome County: GE F111 Contract, Broome County: Greenwood Road, Broome County: GSA Facility, Broome County: Drug Awareness Center, Broome County: Kroehler Corporation, Broome County: Nanticoke Creek, Broome County: Department of Planning, Broome County: Department of Social Services, Broome County: Stadium Project, Broome County: Metro Interfaith, Broome County: Nezelek, Broome County: Transitional Opportunities Corporation, Broome County: Tri-City Airport, Broome County: Binghamton Education, Broome County: Binghamton State Office Building, Broome County: Wheelchair Lifts, Broome County: Incremental Energy Associates, Broome County: Binghamton 201 Facilities Plan, Broome County: Binghamton Upper Front Street, Broome County: Kirkwood Industrial Park Access Ramps, Broome County: Roberson Center, Broome County: Interstate Route 88.
- District Issues 095, 1976 - 1978 (Box 101)
  Sullivan - Mamakating, Sullivan - Monticello, Sullivan - Monticello - Housing Authority, Sullivan - Monticello - Periwinkle Productions, Sullivan - Monticello - Stergis Arts, Sullivan - Liberty - village, Sullivan - Stone Arch Bridge, Sullivan - Highland, Sullivan - Lumberland, Sullivan - Liberty, Sullivan - Liberty - Sewer Project, Sullivan - Liberty - Flooding Project, Sullivan - Neversink, Sullivan - Neversink - Disaster Relief, Sullivan - Rockland, Sullivan - Roscoe, Sullivan - Roscoe Fire Department, Sullivan - Thompson, Sullivan - Tusten, Sullivan - Woodbridge, Sullivan - Wurtsboro, Target Mailings - lists and inter-office, Target Mailings - (governmental), Target Mailings - (non-governmental), Ulster - Community Action, Ulster - UCCC, Ulster - EDA Designation, Ulster - Emunah Farms, Ulster - Energy Council, Ulster - Federated Sportsmen’s Club, Ulster - Lake Minnewaska, Ulster - County Legislature, Ulster - Minnewaska, Ulster - Mid-Hudson School Study Council, Ulster - Miscellaneous, Ulster - Pilot Transportation, Ulster - Rescue Squad, Ulster - Route 209, Ulster - Traver Hollow Bridge, Ulster - Youth Conservation Corps, Ulster - Bloomingburg, Ulster - Ellenville, Ulster - Ellenville - Urban Renewal Housing, Ulster - Denning, Ulster - Gardiner, Ulster - Hurley, Ulster - Kingston, Ulster - Marbletown, Ulster - New Paltz - Quigley Sheridan Alternative Energy, Ulster - New Paltz - town, Ulster - New Paltz - village, Ulster - Olive, Ulster - Rochester - town, Ulster - Rosendale - village, Ulster - Rosendale - town, Ulster - Rosendale Park Fund, Ulster - SBA Disaster Designation, Ulster - Shandaken, Ulster - Warwarsing, Ulster - USPS, Ulster - Walkill Flood Control Project, Ulster - Woodstock - County Women’s Home, Ulster - Woodstock - Cliff Problems, Ulster - Woodstock - Woodstock Estates, Ulster - Woodstock - Sidewalk Project, Ulster - Woodstock.
- District Issues 095, circa 1977 (Box 104)
  Public Works - Regulations and Information, Public Works - Employment Act, Public Works - Sullivan County Court House, Public Works - Correspondence, Southern Tier East Regional Planning, EPA Funds for NYS 1977, Health Systems Agenices, Mid-Hudson Legal Service, Upper Delaware Regional Water Resources Planning Board, Post Office Closings, Public Works - Delaware County, Public Works - Mailings to Local Officials, Hudson Flow Skimming, Tocks Island Dam, Federal Energy Regulatory Commission Prattsville NY DEIS 1978, Prattsville, Mid-Hudson Regional Energy Council, Nuclear Power Plants.
- District Issues 095, circa 1977 (Box 137)
  Ulster - Shandaken, Ulster - Shandaken - Phoenicia Bridge, Ulster - Warwarsing, Ulster - Woodstock - Cliff Problem, Ulster - Woodstock - Town, Ulster - General Miscellaneous, Multi-County - Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, Multi-County - Catskill Study Commission, Multi-County - Soil Conservation Service, Multi-County - Delaware River Basin Commission, Multi-County - Disaster Winter 1977, Multi-County - EPA Grants Funds, NYS Allocation 1977, Multi-County - Hudson Skim, Multi-County - Utility Rate Increases, Multi-County - Broome/Tioga Association for Mentally Retarded, Multi-County - Fall 1977 Agricultural Disaster, Multi-County - NY/PA Health Service Area, Multi-County - Nuclear Power Plants, Multi-County - Prattsville Pump Storage Facility, Multi-County - Southern Tier Planning and Development Board, Multi-County - Southern Tier Eastern Region Planning and Development, Multi-County - Susquehanna River Study, Multi-County - Mid-Hudson Valley Legal Services, Multi-County - Broome/Tioga/Tompkins Disaster July 1986, Multi-County - Susquehanna River Basin Committee, Multi-County - Tocks Island Dam (3 files).
- District Issues 095, circa 1978 (Box 283)
  Delaware River Materials.
- District Issues 096, 1978 - 1980 (Box 134)
  Parts of the district were designated a labor surplus area, prompting MFM correspondence to businesses within it. Files:, Auto Parts, Federal Assistance to Business Information Sheet, Services, Communications, Cleaners, Building Trades, Hotels/Restaurants, Food Suppliers, Customer Services, Special Interest, Electronics, Manufacturers, Random Correspondence, Grants within District, NRA Grants, HUD Grants. Project Files by County: Sullivan, Tompkins (3 files), Ulster, Delaware, Chemung, Tioga, Multi-County, Broome (2 files). Rosendale Bath House, Ten files for 1979 meeting within the district.
- District Issues 096, 1978 - 1980 (Box 254)
  Prattsville Pump Storage 1978-1980, Hudson River HR4788 1979.
- District Issues 096, 1978 - 1980 (Box 280)
  Farmer’s Home Administration (FmHA) - Construction Program, FmHA - Soil and Water Program, FmHA - Business Program, FmHA - Farm Program, FmHA - Women’s Education Program, FmHA - Housing Program, FmHA - Miscellaneous Program, Fire Departments Assistance, Small Business Administration, D of State, D of Transportation, Veteran’s Administration, Public Works, Public Works “Round 2" (2 files), Public Works “Round 2" - Tompkins County, Public Works “Round 2" - Sullivan County, Public Works “Round 2" - Chemung County, Public Works “Round 2" - Tioga County, Public Works “Round 2" - Delaware County, Public Works “Round 2" - Broome County, Housing, D of Housing and Urban Development, Solar Energy, Staff Journals, Urban Banker, Urban Development Action Grant, Regulations: D of Energy, Small Cities Meeting 1978, Regulations: D of Labor, Regulations: Flood Plain, Regulations: D of Health, Education, and Welfare, Regulations: D of Interior, Regulations: D of Labor Youth Program, Regulations: Soil Conservation Service, Regulations: Small Business Administration, Regulations: Disaster Assistance, Regulations: Environmental Protection Agency, Regulations: D of Agriculture FmHA.
- District Issues 096, 1978 - 1981 (Box 265)
  Railroads 1981, Grants 1978, Grants 1980, Grants Files (4 files of individual files), Defense Contracts - past awards, Pending Grants - Broome, Pending Grants - Tioga, Pending Grants - Tompkins, NYS Education, NYS Justice, NYS Affordable Housing, NYS NYC, NYS Energy, NYS Labor, NYS Transportation, NYS Mental Health, NYS D of State, NYS Miscellaneous, Delaware Opportunities, Chemung Economic Opportunities Organization, Opportunities for Broome, Multi-County Community Development Projects, Sullivan Communities Action, Tioga Opportunities Program, Tompkins EOC, Ithaca College (3 files), Broome Community College, Ulster Community Action, Ulster Community College, SUNY Binghamton (four files), SUNY Delhi, Ulster county, Sullivan, Tioga, Tompkins, Delaware, Broome.
- District Issues 096, circa 1979 (Box 73)
  Sullivan County - Community Action Agency, Sullivan County Community College, Sullivan County Community College Housing (HUD), Sullivan County - Community General Hopsital, Sullivan County - Department of Public Works, Sullivan County - Fallsburg, Sullivan County - Falls Poultry, Sullivan County - International Airport, Sullivan County - Liberty, Sullivan County - Liberty - Sidewalks, Sullivan County - Liberty - Bridge, Sullivan County - Liberty - Village, Sullivan County - Mamakating, Sullivan County - Miscellaneous, Sullivan County - Monticello - Sleepy Hollow, Sullivan County - Monticello, Sullivan County - Monticello - Housing, Sullivan County - Monticello - Thompson Sewers, Sullivan County - Mountain Pride Farms, Sullivan County - Neversink Flooding, Sullivan County - Neversink, Sullivan County - Office of Aging, Bulk Third Class Rates, Sullivan County - Parks & Recreation, Sullivan County - Planning Board, Sullivan County - Politics, Sullivan County - Public Information, Sullivan County - Roscoe, Sullivan County - Airport, Sullivan County - Urban Mass Transportation Administration, Sullivan County - Woodridge, Sullivan County - Big Vanilla, Sullivan County - Wurtsboro, Sullivan County - Wurtsboro: Max ALTMAN, New York State D of State, New York State D of Transportation Sign Removal, D of Transportation, D of Interior, Ulster County - Ulster County Community College, Ulster County - Ellenville, Ulster County - Ellenville: People’s League, Ulster County - Ellenville: Housing Urban Renewal, Ulster County - Ellenville: Richie’s Enterprises, Ulster County Energy Plan, Ulster County - Gateway to the Catskills - Steamtown, Ulster County - High Falls, Ulster County - Hurley, Ulster County - Minnewaska, Ulster County - Miscellaneous, Ulster County - New Paltz: Community Gardens, Ulster County - New Paltz: town, Ulster County - SUNY New Paltz, Ulster County - Olive, Ulster County - Rochester, Ulster County - Rosendale Women’s Studio, Ulster County - Rosendale Park Funds, Ulster County - Rosendale, town, Ulster County - Route 209, Ulster County - Wawarsing, Ulster County - Wood for Fuel (2 files), Ulster County - Woodstock: Zema Road, Ulster County - Woodstock: Route 375, Ulster County - Woodstock: town, Ulster County - Woodstock: McGIVEN, United States Postal Service.
- District Issues 097, 1979 - 1982 (Box 154)
  Tompkins - Newfield, Delaware - Bovina, Delaware - Delhi - Village, Delaware - Delhi - County Office Building, Delaware - Downsville, Delaware - Fleischmanns, Delaware - Halcottsville, Delaware - Hamden, Delaware - Harpersfield, Delaware - Hobart, Delaware - Kortright, Delaware - Margaretville, Delaware - Meredith, Delaware - Middletown, Delaware - Roxbury - Town, Delaware - Stamford, Delaware - Walton, Delaware - Walton - Town, Delaware - Walton - Section 8 Housing, Sullivan - Bethel, Sullivan - Cocheton, Sullivan - Delaware, Sullivan - Forestburgh, Sullivan - Highland, Sullivan - Lumberland, Sullivan - Mamakating, Sullivan - Tompson, Sullivan - Tusten, Chemung - Miscellaneous 1982, Chemung - Miscellaneous, Chemung - CWA Teleprompter, Chemung - Regional Housing Council, Chemung - Chemung - Town, Chemung - Erin, Chemung - Newtown-Hoffman Creek Dam, Chemung - Van Etten, Chemung - County Watershed Project.
- District Issues 097, 1980, 1981 (Box 90)
  1980 Ulster Flood, 1981 Ulster Energy Conference, 1981 Wind Power, 1980-1981 Gypsy Moths, 1980-1981 SBA Disaster Loans, 1980-1981 HUD, FHA, FmHA Constituent Cases.
- District Issues 097, 1980 - 1983 (Box 259)